-老板 这是给你的 -不 不用这样
-Boss. This for you. -No, no, no. Come on.
我不能占你家人的便宜
I can't impose on your family.
不行
No.
雅斯敏特意为你准备的
Yasmin, she made this just for you.
老板 收下吧
Jefe, please.
拿着
Take it.
那替我谢谢她
Tell her thank you.
好的
Yeah.
你看
So, listen.
今天会很辛苦
Today's gonna be hard.
整天都要应付检查
We got inspections all day.
要填表格 拆表格
Forms to build, forms to break down
还要应付送货的
and deliveries all gettin' in our way.
今天咱们加油干活
We work hard today,
会有奖金
there'll be a bonus for ya.
大家下班时
And let's all go home
手指头一根都别少
with the same amount of fingers that we came with.
明白
All right.
兄弟们
Hermanos.
好好干 开工吧
Have a good day. Let's get it.
-早 杰西 -早 莱文
-Morning, Jess. -Buenos dias, Levon.
-还好吗？-挺好的
-How you doing? -I'm good.
-谢谢 -嘿 莱文
-Gracias. -Hey, Levon.
今天没人找你借钱吧？
No one's been asking you for money today?
还没
No.
-怎么？-因为 很显然
-Why? -Because, apparently,
全家只有我
I am the only person in the family
一个人会做供应商账目
who can do the vendor accounting.
让一让！
Oh, excuse me!
看来我们是邪恶父母啊 亲爱的 对吗？
Hey, I guess we're evil parents, babe, huh?
就因为她得干几小时活？
'Cause we make her work a couple hours.
今天没空和你吵
Not today.
先把付款单处理完行吗？
How about you get those disbursements done, huh?
外面一堆卡车等着结账
We got a line of trucks out there that need paying.
可以给我结账啊
You could pay me.
结什么账？
Pay you for what?
付我过去十九年的房租
For 19 years of free rent,
伙食费 中学学费
and groceries, and high school,
大学学费 化妆品 空手道课？
college, makeup, karate classes?
-还要我继续列吗？-不用了
-You want me to keep goin'? -Really? No. It's okay.
莱文 签个字行吗？
Levon, can you sign that, please?
-爸？-干嘛？
-Dad? -What?
-今天乱成一锅粥 -我知道
-Today is a total shitshow. -I know.
你还把三件事排同一时间
And you scheduled three things at once.
她错得没说
She's not wrong.
您好 这里是加西亚家族建筑公司
Hi, yeah. This is Garcia and Family Construction.
我是卡拉 你们让我等了挺久
Yeah, you're speaking with Carla, you've had me on hold for a bit now.
今天能按时送货对吧？
So, we're gettin' those deliveries today, right?
行 我继续等
Yeah, I'll hold.
这是今晚要用的清单
This is what I need for tonight.
太夸张了吧！这是要结婚吗？
That's insane. What is that? Is that for your wedding or something?
不 今晚用
No, it's for tonight.
我们学期结束了 要庆祝
We finished the semester, so we're gonna celebrate.
你才读完一个学期
I mean, you just finished one semester.
-对 这是重要里程碑 -是吗？
-Right. It's a big milestone. -Is it?
-现在流行这个？-听着 这已经算克制了
-Is that a thing? -Look, it could be worse, okay?
-我在众筹 -嗯 好
-Look, I'm passing the hat. -Mm-hmm. Yeah.
-够租派对巴士 -天啊
-That gets us a party van. -Oh, my God.
订个包间吃饭
Locks in a private room for dinner.
拼命省钱而已
Just saving like crazy.
嗯 我需要绑定一张信用卡
Yeah. I just need a card on file.
闺女 我没……
Mija, I can't. I don't...
闺女……
Mija...
算了 我不要了
Okay, fine. I don't need it.
给她想要的吧
Just give her what she wants.
妈 我能自己争取
No, Mom, I can fight my own battles.
没人质疑这点
Oh, no, no, nobody's arguing that.
谁不需要派对巴士呢？
I mean, everybody needs a party bus, right?
考完试庆祝一下 给
After they finish one semester. Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 凯特
Hey, Kate.
让一让
Excuse me.
他该回去干活了
He needs to get back to work.
滚蛋 关你屁事
Get the fuck out of here. It's not your business.
我没事 老板
I'm good, boss.
真没事 五分钟就好
All good. Five minutes.
嘿！
Hey!
我够客气了
I was respectful.
你才没有
You weren't.
滚出去 起来
Get outta here. Get up.
别再回来
Don't come back.
-走吧 -走
-Vamonos. -Vamonos.
没事吧？
You okay?
你怎么做到的？
How did you do that?
回去干活
We need to get back to work.
这个 搬到右边
This one. Over to the right.
-好的 -谢了 凯特
-You got it. -Thanks, Kate.
莱文！我靠！
Levon! Holy fuck!
那是军队学的招式？
Was that some military shit?
你什么都没看到
You didn't see anything.
要是我爸知道 他会气炸
If Dad knew, he'd shit bricks.
能教我吗？
Can you teach me?
我爷爷是伞兵
Look, my grandpa, he was a paratrooper.
教我怎么掰手指
Taught me how to break fingers,
追踪野兽
track animals.
掰手指？
Break fingers?
对
Yeah.
奶奶给你做了辣炖鸡（墨西哥名菜）
Grandma made you tinga. Shredded chicken.
很好
It's good.
还有奶奶手做的玉米饼
And Grandma made you some handmade grandma tortillas.
为什么总有人投喂我？
Why is everyone always feeding me?
如果我们没投喂你 那你就只配吃金枪鱼罐头和花生酱
If we don't, you'll just eat canned tuna and peanut butter.
你什么都没看到 懂吗？
You didn't see anything, okay?
告密没好下场
Snitches get stitches.
我需要时给我撑腰就行
Just get my back if I ever need it.
当然 珍妮
Sure, Jenny.
回见
See ya.
爱你 爸爸
Love you, Daddy.
我也爱你 宝贝 上车吧
Love you, too, honey. Get in the truck.
什么情况？
What's the occasion?
没什么事
No occasion.
梅瑞狄斯要招待朋友
Meredith's entertaining some friends.
对
Yeah.
我不知道今天是你探视日
I didn't realize today was your visitation.
你可以让她留下
You could let her stay.
求你了罗斯医生 没必要这样
Yeah, please, Doctor Roth, we don't have to do this.
她妈妈需要你时你不在
You weren't there when her mother needed you
梅瑞狄斯需要你时你也不会在
and you won't be there when Meredith needs you,
但我会
but I will.
我知道
Oh, I know.
你想打我
You want to strike me.
你只会这一招
It's your only answer.
暴力
Violence.
你是个危险的父亲
You're an unsafe parent.
你是杀人犯
You're a killer.
别假装你不是
You can't pretend that you're not.
打扰了 罗斯医生
Excuse me, Doctor Roth.
今天是我的日子
Today's my day.
你外公为什么在我探视日开派对？
Why's your grandfather throwing a party on my day?
我饿坏了 还没吃饭
I'm super hungry. I didn't eat.
在等你
I was waiting for you.
真的？
You were?
嗯
Yeah.
好 走吧
Okay. Let's go.
-给你 -谢谢
-Here you go. -Thank you.
-谢谢 -慢用
-Thank you. -Enjoy.
不用你买东西
I don't need you buying stuff.
打开看看
Come on. Open it.
是妈妈
It's Mama.
这张照片
I took that picture
是我爸给我的胶片相机拍的
with a film camera my dad gave me.
外公把妈妈的照片都收起来了
Grandpa took all of Mama's pictures down.
有时我都快忘了她的样子
Sometimes I forget what she looks like.
她长得像你
She looks like you.
爸 我能说件事吗？
Dad, can I tell you something?
什么都能说
Anything.
我生妈妈的气
I'm mad at Mama.
气她丢下我们走了
For dying and leaving us.
没关系的
It's okay.
我也很难过
I hurt, too.
马特现在见你
Matt will see you now.
他在我的探视时间给她办派对
He's throwing parties for her during my visitation time.
盯着我嘲笑
Staring at me, laughing.
他在激怒你
He's baiting you.
等你挥拳头
Hoping you throw a punch.
不会的
Nah.
那样他就赢了
Then he wins.
对方律师指控你
Opposing counsel
因服役导致未治愈的PTSD
alleges you have untreated PTSD
和脑损伤 有暴力倾向
and brain trauma from your military service, making you at-risk for violence.
我为出生国英国效力22年
I served Britain, the country of my birth, for 22 years.
现在反倒成坏人了？
I'm the fuckin' bad guy for it?
还有更糟的
It gets worse.
他们要求探视需监督
They're requesting supervised visits
探视时间从每周两小时
and a reduction in visitation from two hours a week
减到每两周一小时
to one hour every two.
我必须反抗
I have to fight this.
我存了一万块
I have ten grand saved up.
睡卡车里存的？
From sleeping in your truck?
法庭不会喜欢你
Court won't be thrilled
居无定所
by your lack of a fixed residence.
我会解决的
Hey, I'll figure it out.
罗斯医生为什么这么恨你？
Why does Doctor Roth hate you so much?
他觉得我害死了他闺女
He thinks I killed his daughter.
是你吗？
Did you?
是自杀
It was suicide.
我当时在国外执行任务
I was overseas on a deployment.
她一生都在对抗抑郁
She battled depression her whole life.
知道消耗战吗？
You've heard of attrition warfare?
知道 慢慢拖垮敌人
Yeah. You grind the enemy down slowly.
这家伙有团队
This guy's got a team
时薪千元的律师
of thousand-dollar-an-hour attorneys
会榨干你
who will bleed you dry
直到你化为尘埃
until you turn to dust and blow away.
我们只能谈判投降
The best we can do is negotiated surrender.
你有闺女吗？
You have a daughter?
给你们带了点东西
I got you guys a little somethin'.
尼娜
Nina.
乔丝琳……
Jocelyn...
-香特尔 还有露比 -谢谢 妈妈
-Chantel. And Rubi. -Thanks, Mama.
老兄 这太棒了！
Dude, these are insane!
哪儿搞的？
Where'd you get these?
我有亲戚 七八个吧
I have a cousin. Or seven.
干杯 婊子们！
Salud , bitches!
谢谢
Thank you.
干杯
Shots.
嘿！
Hey!
干嘛？干嘛？干嘛？
What? What? What?
我们还在这儿干嘛？
What the fuck are we still doing here?
他说要"那个"
He said he wants the One.
"我要那个 我要他妈的那个"
"I want the One. I want the fucking One."
这他妈什么意思？
What the fuck does that mean?
他见到就知道 懂？
He'll know it when he sees her, okay?
你知道这单
Do you know how much fuckin' money
能赚多少吗？
we're gonna make on this?
-最好如此 -享受吧 嗯？
-We better. -Enjoy, yeah?
最后一家店
Hey, last establishment.
你们早班飞机
You guys have early flights.
后面那张桌空着吗？
Is that back table open?
告诉我名字就给你
It's yours if you tell me your name.
珍妮
It's Jenny.
我是强尼
Hi, I'm Johnny.
你好 强尼
Hi, Johnny.
这边请
Right here.
兄弟
My man.
你不止会做PPT
You are more than a pitch deck.
尼娜？
Nina?
-尼娜 别吐 -我没事
-Nina, don't throw up. -I'm fine.
她一脸要吐的样子
She's making her puke face.
-带她去厕所 -真恶心
-Let's get you to a bathroom. -Oh, ew.
廉价货！晦气！
Cheap! Bad energy.
呃
Ew!
天啊
Oh, my God.
我现在恨死你了 一点不好笑
I hate you so much right now, it's not funny.
有点好笑吧
It's kinda funny.
天 我丑爆了
Oh, my God, I look mad busted.
这样没法出去见人
I cannot go out there like this.
挑重点补妆吧 30分钟后出发
Okay, well, pick your battles, 'cause we're leavin' in 30.
操！
Fuck!
快走
Go.
珍妮失踪了
Jenny's missing.
什么叫"失踪"？
What do you mean, "missing"?
她周五和朋友们出去后没回来
She went out with her friends on Friday.
周六我们报警了
Saturday, we were worried, so we called the cops,
周日……
and then on Sunday...
她周日晚上有钢琴演奏会
She had a piano recital on Sunday night.
请了半个家族的人
We invited half our family.
我表姐迪诺拉是费城警监
My cousin Dinora is a Police Captain in Philly,
说警方不会认真查这种案子
and she says they don't work these cases.
立个案就忘了
They take a report and forget about it.
你能帮我们吗？
Can you help us?
我能让工地运转顺畅
I can keep the site running smoothly.
不 帮我们找珍
No. Help us find Jen.
我爸是绿色贝雷帽
My dad was a Green Beret.
你们这种人我一眼就能认出
I can see you guys comin' a mile away.
你们追捕坏人
You hunt bad guys.
你们跳伞突袭
You jump outta planes.
解决那些坏人
And you get those bad guys.
我现在不一样了
I'm a different person now.
好吧
All right, well,
也许这个能帮她
maybe this'll help her.
这是五十元
Here, it's 50.
拿着
Take it.
还有二十元当经费
We have another 20 for expenses.
拿着吧 兄弟
Come on, just take it, man.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
[file name]: 111.txt
[file content begin]
我们还有二十元用作开销
We have another 20 for expenses.
拜托 拿着吧兄弟
Come on, just take it, man.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
那已经不是现在的我了
It's not who I am anymore.
枪叔 是我啊！
Gunny, it's me!
别杀我！
Don't kill me!
我带了牛排！
I got steaks!
你要是往左偏一英尺 我就死了
If you'd shot a foot to the left, I'd be dead.
如果我想你死 你早没命了
If I wanted you dead, you'd be dead.
你知道吗 对我来说
You know, for me,
白天和黑夜没有界限
there's no separation between day and night.
所以我得自己创造界限
So, I got to make my own.
活在这个灰暗的世界真难
It's hard livin' in a gray world.
我没能保住你的眼睛
I couldn't save your eyes.
对不起
Sorry.
这让我寝食难安
That eats at me.
不
No.
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
要不是你及时出现把我拽走
Joyce would be burying tags in the back yard
乔伊斯现在就得在院子里埋我的狗牌了
if you hadn't come along, scooped me up and ran.
她叫什么名字？
What's her name?
珍妮
Jenny.
珍妮 好
Jenny. All right.
她是个好孩子吗？
She a good kid?
她是个很棒的孩子
She's a great kid.
听着 你要做这事 就得全力以赴
Now, you do this, you better lock in.
绝不能半途而废
You better go full on, no half-measures.
但只要你做到了 上帝会保佑他们
But you do, God help 'em.
我跟珍妮说过会保护她
I told Jenny I had her back.
呃……
Well, uh...
我想你
I miss ya.
我担心你
I worry about ya,
但你没必要专程跑来假装征求我的同意
but you didn't have to come down here and pretend that
反正你早就下定决心了
you needed my permission for something
你早就拿定主意了
you already made your mind up about.
进来吧 该吃饭了
Get in here. We're eating.
嘿 卡拉
Hey, Carla.
谢谢你能来
Thanks for coming.
他在哪儿？
Where is he?
楼上 左边第一个门
Upstairs. First door on your left.
《月光奏鸣曲》
"Moonlight Sonata".
-对 -弹得真美
-Yeah. -It's beautiful.
她为了去商学院拒绝了音乐奖学金
She turned down a music scholarship
说要像她爸爸一样
to go to business school.
想当个地产大亨
She wanted to be like her pops.
做大型土地开发
Be a big land developer.
她会的
And she will.
嗯
Yeah.
不用了 谢谢
Nah. No, thanks.
你的家人需要希望
Your family needs hope.
但我没法以这副模样面对他们
But I can't face 'em like this.
我妻子去世后
When my wife passed,
我离开了皇家海军陆战队
and I left the Royal Marines,
很多人都觉得我废了
a lot of people would've given up on me.
但你们对我很有耐心
But you were patient with me.
-你 卡拉 珍妮 -珍妮
-You, Carla, Jenny. -Jenny.
你们就是我的家人
You're my family.
看着我 兄弟
Look at me, brother.
我会带她回家
I'm gonna bring her home.
我保证
I promise.
我一定会带她回家
I'm gonna bring her home.
"斯基普酒吧"
"Skip's Bar."
非常感谢 不错吧兄弟？
Thank you very much. Good, bro?
你没事吧？嗯？
You good? Yeah?
你怎么样？
How you doing?
你需要来点餐后酒提提神
You need a little aperitif, you know?
好吧
All right.
嘿 小子 走错门了
Oh, yo. Wrong house, kid.
滚出去
Get the fuck out.
你好啊 强尼
Hello, Johnny.
想赛跑吗？看谁赢？
Wanna have a race? See who wins?
双手举起来 站起来
Hands up. Stand up.
手指交叉放在脑后
Place your fingers behind your head.
你是条子？
You a cop?
你巴不得我是条子
You wish I was a cop.
你的冒险结束了 小子
Your adventure, kid.
那女孩在哪儿？
Where's the girl?
什么女孩？
What girl?
失踪的女孩
The missing girl.
你朋友从酒吧后门掳走的那个
The one your friends snatched outta the back of the bar.
我告诉过条子 她自己喝醉跑了
I told the cops. She ran off. Drunk or somethin'.
这傻逼连酒都拿不稳
Fuckin' poobutt can't hold her drink.
关我屁事？
How's that my problem?
人会说谎
People lie.
你撒谎吗 强尼？
Do you lie, Johnny?
我不相信人
I don't trust people.
我只信生物学
I trust biology.
我们的生理反应都一样
We're all wired the same.
给老子起来
Get the fuck up.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
你的大脑知道自己在浴缸里
Your mind knows you're in the bathtub
只是盖了条湿毛巾
and it's just a wet towel.
但肾上腺素会让心跳加速
But adrenaline makes your heart race,
耗氧量增加
so you burn more air.
神经系统会误以为你在溺水
Your nervous system tells you that you're drowning.
你老板知道你在吧台贩毒吗？
Your bosses know you deal dope over the bar top?
偷收银机的钱？
Steal from the till?
操你妈！
Fuck you!
你知道这些人手段多狠
You know these guys are next level.
他们会灭人满门
They wipe out entire fucking bloodlines.
有道理
Fair enough.
但你要明白 名字我拿定了
Just know you're giving me names.
方式你选
Your choice how.
强尼？
Johnny?
你在哪儿 兄弟？
Where are you, brother?
在等帮手？
You're expecting company?
操 当然在等
Damn fuckin' right, I am.
开门！不然宰了你！
Open the door. Fuckin' kill you.
俄国佬
Russians.
该死
Fuck.
对不起 妈妈
I'm sorry, Mom.
我为……感到抱歉
I'm sorry for...
用成就的外衣……
shielding myself...
包裹真实的自己
in a blanket of accomplishments.
多希望你能看到……
I wish you could've seen me...
真实的我
who I really am.
只想和你一样坚强
Just want to be strong like you.
我为什么在这儿？
What am I doing here?
最好开着免提 让你亲耳听听 老板
on speaker It's better you see for yourself, boss.
不是什么大事
It's not a big problem.
你们两个他妈干了什么？
What the fuck have you two done, huh?
他们为什么互相开枪？
Why'd they shoot each other?
这太不专业了
This is very unprofessional.
强尼没分寸 是个懦夫
Johnny has no control. He's a weak man.
可能他说疯话 然后就突突了
Maybe he talk crazy, and then it's bang-bang time.
-"突突"？-对啊
-"Bang-bang time"? -Yeah.
突突时间
Bang-bang time.
发现有什么不同吗？
You notice anything different?
你的发型
Your hair.
白痴
Idiot.
我的钱呢？
Where is my fucking money?
你觉得这是抢劫？
You think this was a robbery?
不可能
Impossible.
没人敢抢我们 除非又蠢又疯
No one would rob us. No one is that stupid,
或者既蠢又疯
or that crazy.
这是霰弹枪伤口
This is a shotgun wound.
看到霰弹枪了吗？
You see any shotguns?
-嗯？-少了九捆
-Hmm? -That's nine bands missing.
我们的九万美金不见了！
Ninety thousand dollars of our fucking money!
是赛蒙的钱
It's Symon's money.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, sweetheart.
爸爸你在干嘛？
Hey, Daddy, what are you doing?
呃 没什么 就在……
Uh, nothin'. Just, uh...
处理点工作
Just some work.
-你在学校吗？-对
-Are you in school? -Yeah.
这时候该用学校电话打给我吗？
You supposed to be calling me from school?
不该
No.
一切都好吗？
Everything okay?
嗯 就想说声"嗨" 爱你爸爸
Yeah, I just wanted to say, "hi." Love you, Daddy.
我也爱你
Love you, too.
拜
Bye.
这门他妈会自动开？
The fucking door opens itself?
我不喜欢这样
I don't like this.
整晚床上就我一人
I'm alone in the bed all night.
你吃
You eat.
来床上躺会儿
You come to bed for a bit.
你以为钱是从天上掉下来的？
You think the money falls from the sky?
希望你不介意
Hope you don't mind.
我饿了
I was hungry.
觉得我们可以聊聊
Thought we could have a little chat.
我要撕胶带了
I'm gonna take the tape off.
但如果你控制不住音量……
But if you can't control your volume...
就下水待着
You go in the water.
你知道我是谁吗？
Do you know who I am?
我需要知道吗？
Should I?
你显然不知道自己惹了谁
You clearly have no idea who you fuck with.
尽管自嗨 说出来
Make yourself happy. Tell me.
你听说过我们吗？
You have heard of us?
当然
I have.
真的？
Really?
"盗贼"
The Vor.
兄弟会 盗贼联盟
The Bratva. The Brothers.
现在怎么自称都行
The League of Thieves.
随便你们俄国黑帮
Whatever Russian gangsters
现在喜欢叫什么
like to call themselves these days.
看来你有点来头
You clearly are somebody.
你杀了兄弟会的士兵
You slaughter Vory soldiers.
偷兄弟会的钱
You steal Vory money.
这是个误会
It was a misunderstanding.
我是高层成员
I am a brother of high rank.
你和所有相关的人
You and all connected with you,
会被追杀三代
will be hunted for three generations.
对 我猜到了
Yep. I assumed so.
我们都知道如果不好好处理
We all know how these things play out
事情会闹得多大
if you don't keep them tidy.
操你妈！
Fuck you!
这一拳是为你今早打女人
That's for slapping that woman this morning.
那是我老婆
That woman was my wife.
这一拳是为你打老婆
That's for slapping your wife.
你的钱在这儿
Here's your money.
我不是贼
I'm not a thief.
我对你们的生意没兴趣
I don't care about your business.
我在找一个姑娘
I'm lookin' for a young lady.
我……我不明白
I... I don't understand.
你们用来做脏事的酒吧
The bar you do your dirty business out of,
有个19岁女孩被绑架了
a 19 year-old girl was kidnapped.
我在找她
I'm lookin' for her.
迪米
Dimi.
你最好小点声
Maybe you should keep your voice down.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
交出那女孩
Gimme the girl,
大家相安无事
and everybody goes about their business.
一个女孩？
A girl?
就为这搞这么大动静？
All of this is for a girl?
没人会杀三个人就为卖个女人
No one kills three people to sell a woman.
没人
No one.
我不是要卖她
I'm not selling her.
我要带她回家
I'm gonna bring her home.
不达目的誓不罢休
Not stopping until I do.
你是谁？
Who are you?
你是什么人？
What are you?
操你妈
Fuck you.
我操你妈
操你妈！
Fuck you!
好了 谈完了
Okay, we're done.
迪米
Dimi.
你是谁 迪米？
Who are you, Dimi?
他收钱
He takes money.
他留钱
He leaves money.
他杀人如麻
He kills without fear.
问题是为什么？
The question is why?
沃洛曾是受人尊敬的体面人
Wolo was a respected man of honor,
但他儿子跟我们不是一路人
but his son was never like us.
迪米不是生意人
Dimi is not a businessman.
他喜欢捣乱胜过正经工作
He prefers mischief over hard work.
每天都在践踏他父亲的心血
He spits on his father's heart every fucking day.
找到这个人
Find this man.
带他来见我
And bring him to me.
我叫珍妮·加西亚
My name is Jenny Garcia.
父亲是乔
My father is Joe.
母亲是卡拉
My mother is Carla.
你们抓错人了 这是个误会
You have the wrong girl. This is a mistake.
他们是假的
They're not real.
你也是假的
You're not real.
这……
This...
他妈的是真的
is fucking real.
吃你的饭
Eat your fuckin' food,
然后换上衣服
then you put on the fucking clothes
-再他妈闭嘴！-操你妈！
-and shut the fuck up! -Fuck you!
见过人死前的样子吗？
Have you ever seen someone die before?
眼睛会瞬间蒙上阴翳
Their eyes just cloud right over.
啧啧 你可真漂亮
Mmm. You're so fuckin' pretty. Huh?
对吧 小公主？
Aren't you, Princess?
吃你的饭！
Eat your fuckin' food!
[file name]: 111.txt
[file content begin]
听说白袜队要在南卢普区
Believe the idea the
建新球场的消息
White Sox are in serious talks
就在罗斯福路旁的芝加哥河畔第78区
to build a new stadium in the South Loops, The 78,
这选址太棒了
the location by the Chicago River just off Roosevelt.
能参与南卢普区新球场项目
I love the idea of being in serious talks
我简直兴奋坏了
for a new stadium in the South Loop.
最近混得咋样？搞承包发大财了吧？
How's it goin', cat? Getting rich contracting?
是啊 天天灌水泥
Oh, yeah. Pouring concrete more like.
早不混这行了 现在是正经纳税人
I'm outta the game. I'm an honest taxpayer now.
见过枪叔吗？他最近如何？
You talked to Gunny? How's he doing?
前阵子见过 过得挺滋润
Saw him the other day. He's happy.
你没事可不会找我
Well, you never call me unless you need something,
说吧 想要什么？
so, what do you want?
找个叫迪米的家伙
Lookin' for someone called Dimi.
应该是迪米特里 沃洛迪米尔·科林斯尼克的手下
Probably Dimitri. An associate of Wolodymyr Kolisnyk.
那可是大人物啊兄弟
That's a high-ranking dude, cat.
黑手党头目
Mafia captain.
正牌兄弟会话事人
Legit Bratva shot caller.
这种狠角色可惹不起
Not a guy you wanna fuck with.
当然不会
Nah, never.
这个迪米可能涉及
This Dimi fella,
人口贩卖的勾当
he might be involved in human trafficking.
能查查NADDIS和NCIC系统吗？
Can you check NADDIS and NCIC? See if you can get a hit?
我得小心点
I gotta be careful,
不过乔利埃特有家哈蒂酒吧
but there's a bar called Hattie's in Joliet,
是俄国佬的冰毒窝点
where they sell meth for the Russians.
或许该去喝一杯
Maybe you should get a beer there.
谢了兄弟
Nice one. Thanks.
嘿 喝点什么？
Hey. Whatcha havin'?
随便来瓶啤酒
I'll just have a beer. You pick.
行
Okay.
稀客啊 最近去哪混了？
Oh, hey, stranger. Where you been?
忙着赚钱
Tryin' to make a buck.
听说
You know,
你和你的混蛋老哥
rumor has it you and your shitbag brother
在跟俄国佬搭线
have been talkin' to the Russians.
还有人说你们嗨过头
Rumor has it you were so high,
在毒窝误杀大麦克
you accidentally killed Big Mike in a trap house
还栽赃给抢劫团伙
and blamed it on a robbery crew.
操 给老子闭嘴
Fuckin' shut up. Fuckin'...
要是荷兰佬知道有人背着他接触俄国佬
Dutch finds out anybody's talkin' to the Russians but him,
非得发疯不可
he's gonna lose his fuckin' mind.
嘘！
Shh!
认识这人吗？
Do you know this guy?
从没见过
No. I've never seen him.
看着不顺眼
I don't like him.
像个条子
Looks like a cop.
他兜里揣着枪
He's got a gun in his pocket.
像点38口径的 看见没？
Like a .38. You see it?
操 看见了
Fuck. Yes.
该你上了小子
You're up, kid.
跟我来
Follow me.
去和那人聊聊
Go talk to the man.
找什么呢？
You lookin' for somethin'?
我只对药品生意感兴趣
My interests are strictly pharmaceutical, brother.
带枪是几个意思？
Any reason why you packin' heat, brah?
带着现金呢
I'm carrying money.
防着拿刀抢劫的
Hate to lose it to a man with a knife.
他是条子
He's a cop.
你是警察吗？
Are you a cop?
不是 你是？
Nah. Are you?
把兜掏干净 条子
Run your pockets, Chief.
查查有没有警徽
Let's check for that badge.
听见没？
You heard the man.
放桌上
Put it on the table.
立刻！
Fuckin' now.
我来谈生意 不是受侮辱的
I didn't come here to be disrespected.
行吧
All right.
开始吧
Let's play.
拿下他
Get him.
抓住他兄弟
Get him, brother.
再见混蛋
Bye, asshole.
够了！
Enough!
我爷爷说坐着握手不礼貌
My grandpa told me to never shake hands sittin'.
看看这肌肉
Look at those bricks.
你不是条子 是干苦力的
You ain't a cop, you're a working man.
干一辈子建筑了
Been in construction my whole life.
当过兵？
Were you a soldier?
打架像军人
'Cause you fight like a soldier.
尽过义务
I did my part.
空降兵出身
I was Airborne.
训练跳伞结果
They trained us to jump outta planes
最后坐大巴上战场
and we ended up ridin' a bus into combat.
正常操作
Sounds about right.
坐吧兄弟
Have a seat, brother.
听说你要进货
I heard you're in a buyin' mood.
我要蓝玻璃
I'm lookin' for blue glass,
上等货
the good stuff.
长期稳定供应
I need weight. Regular.
每月四磅左右
Like four pounds a month.
就这点？
That's all?
卖给谁？
Who you flippin' it to?
自有渠道
It goes where it's needed.
客户是我的事 不劳费心
The customers are my concern, not yours.
为什么找我们？
And why here? Why us?
芝加哥线人失联了
My Chicago connect is missin' in action.
工地三班倒赶工
I'm runnin' work crews in shifts 24/7.
时间就是金钱
Time is money.
半磅七千刀
Seven K for half a pound.
芝加哥行情价
That's a Chicago price.
五千
Five.
北边高速口
There's a pancake house
有家煎饼屋
at the highway junction straight north of here.
明早七点早餐时间见
Be there, 7:00 a.m., having breakfast.
然后？
And?
带五沓现金
And bring five stacks.
合作愉快
Good talk.
现在滚吧
Now get the fuck outta here.
请坐
Have a seat.
尴尬得像个相亲现场
This is like an awkward Tinder date.
直接给钱吧
Just give her the money.
看啊 果然在这
Mmm. Lo, and behold.
消息传得快
People talk,
钞票更好使
money fucks.
带东西了吗？
You got somethin' for me?
我们可不认识你
We don't know who the fuck you are, brother.
会有人告诉你货在哪
You'll get a call tellin' you where your shit is.
就这样？
That's it?
对 没错
Yeah. Uh-huh.
别耍花样
Don't play me.
我知道你老巢
I know where to find you.
是 你当然知道
Yeah. I guess you do.
谢不杀之恩
Thank you for not shooting me.
操你妈的王八蛋
fuckin' asshole.
-是吗？-准备好
-Yeah? -All right. You ready?
告诉你货在哪
I'm gonna tell you where the skante's at, big dog.
洗耳恭听
I'm waitin'.
座位底下
Under your seat.
-谢了 -留着一次性手机
-Thank you. -Keep the burner phone.
明天联系你
I'mma hit you tomorrow.
倒要看看你们怎么
Then you can tell me how y'all motherfuckers
用我的货一夜暴富
built Rome in a day off my shit.
再谈大宗交易
Then we can talk about weight.
猜猜谁要当一晚公主？
Guess who's gonna be princess for a night?
你们是迪米的得力干将啊
You are Dimi's miracle workers. Huh?
这是给迪米准备的惊喜
And that, that is for Dimi's miracle.
为什么选她？
Why her?
她让我想起父亲别墅里的画像
She reminded me of a painting in one of my father's houses.
带后面去
Take her in the back.
好的
Sure.
看这小可爱们多漂亮
Look how cute these ones are.
像小鲨鱼似的
They look like little sharks.
和你一样可爱
Just like you, cutie.
她咬我！
She bit me!
她应该睡着了啊！
She's supposed to be asleep!
对不起老板
I'm so sorry, sir.
赶紧弄走！
I want her out!
怎样？
Yeah?
他们满意我的货吗？
Did they like my shit?
相当满意
Let's just say they were pleased.
货源充足
There's plenty more where that came from,
但要长期合作
but there's someone you gotta check in with
得先见个人
if we're gonna do business.
什么意思？
What does that mean?
安全措施兄弟
Precautionary measures, brah.
现在联邦按磅判终身监禁
Seein' as the Feds are handin' out life sentences per pound.
这行当不好混
Yeah, this game's not for everyone.
明白兄弟
I hear you, big dog.
给你发个会面邀请
I'mma shoot you an invite for a sit-down.
穿正装带现金
Bring your money and wear a suit.
我没西装
I don't have a suit.
明天就有了
Shit. You will tomorrow.
来的都是顶级人物
'Cause these motherfuckers are as high power as it gets.
我找荷兰佬
I'm here to see someone called Dutch.
这边走
He's right this way.
他在那边
He's over there.
-最近怎样 -荷兰佬
-How you doin'? -Hey, Dutch.
带钱了吗？
You bring the money?
可以吗？
May I?
先把手机给我关机
First, you gotta turn your phone off.
然后呢？
Now what?
钱都给你了
You already have my money.
我是诚心来做生意的
I came here in good faith to do business.
我叫迪米
My name is Dimi.
你呢？
Yours?
比尔
Bill.
比尔·科茨
Bill Coates.
有驾照吗比尔·科茨？
Do you have driver's license, Bill Coates?
什么意思？
Excuse me?
让他查
It's fine. Let him check.
租的车啊
You drive rental.
查过车牌了
We check plates.
抵税用的
Tax write-off.
有问题？
That okay?
这是我生意伙伴
This man is my business partner.
小角色
He is small potatoes.
我才是话事人
I am the big potatoes.
说吧
Tell me.
会惹麻烦吗？
Will you be a problem?
这就是你们的待客之道？
Is this how you do business?
请我来就为威胁？
You invite me here to be threatened?
查清了
Checks out.
刚才失礼了 "威廉"
I apologize for that, "William."
你显然是个
You are clearly a...
正经生意人
serious person.
补货用一次性手机
If you need resupply, use the burner.
发兔子表情
Text bunny rabbit emoji.
兔子表情
Bunny rabbit emoji.
知道我要每月四磅吧？
You made aware I need four pounds a month?
那就发茄子表情
Then text eggplant emoji.
清楚
We are aware.
货满意的话
If you like what is in the case,
继续合作
we do more business.
现在走人别回头
Now, you leave and don't look back.
求之不得
Fine by me.
强尼 你个狗杂种
Johnny, you're a real piece of shit.
阴险的混蛋
You sneaky motherfucker.
嗨混蛋
Hi, asshole.
他来了
He's here.
-操 -扬声器 黑色道奇公羊
-Oh, shit. - -on speakers He's in a black Dodge Ram
藏在树林里
hiding in the trees.
马上到
Okay, we're pulling up now.
行动！
Let's go!
操！他骑摩托跑了！追！
Fuck! He just fuckin' left on a bike! Go!
快追！
Go! Go! Go!
该死！
Fuck!
手举起来
Show me your hands.
当没看见我们
You didn't see us here.
什么都没发生
Nothing fucking happened.
我们接手了
We'll take it from here.
你也是他们的人？
You're on the payroll too?
怎么认识迪米的？
How do you know Dimi?
和迪米什么关系？
What is your business with Dimi?
原来是你们俩混蛋
Ah, you two assholes.
你们淹死的那个人
That man you drowned,
他老婆在健身时
in his own pool while his wife was at Pilates,
是我们叔叔
that man was our uncle.
他太吵了
He wouldn't shut up.
警告过了
I warned him.
-知道我们是谁吗？ -喂
-Do you know who we are, hmm? -Hey. Hey.
老妈给穿花衣服的娘炮
Yeah, people whose ma dresses 'em funny.
这是高级定制
This is fucking couture, man.
是我们的品牌！
It's our fucking brand!
绑腿
Tie up his legs.
想吓唬我？还差点火候
If you want me to be scared, you gotta try harder.
哇！
Whoa!
这是万科
That is Vanko.
这是丹雅
And that is Danya.
我的儿子们
These are my sons.
我的家族血脉
My house and my lineage end
断送在这冰冷钢桌上
on these cold, steel tables.
召开战前会议
Convene the war counsel.
借过 亲爱的
Excuse me, dear.
滚开
Fuck off.
哦豁
Oh, wow.
绝对不可能
Absolutely fuckin' not.
操
Oh, fuck.
没死算你走运
You're lucky you're not already dead.
[file name]: 111.txt
[file content begin]
迪米 我道歉行了吧？
Dimi, apologies, okay?
对不起 我他妈真心道歉
I'm sorry. I'm truly fuckin' sorry.
她他妈咬掉了他的半张脸
She fucking bit half his face off.
-其实不算半张脸 但……-哦
-It wasn't exactly half his face. But...-Oh.
缝了三十六针
Thirty-six stitches.
真够多的
That's a lot.
为了重新缝合他的脸颊
To reattach his cheek.
我是做快活生意的 不是干外科的
I am in the business of pleasure, not surgery.
告诉我……
Tell me...
操
Fuck.
你知道“生意”是什么意思吗？
Do you know what business means?
我……不知道 我是说 知道 操
Do I... No. I mean, yeah. Fuck.
生意的意思是
Business means
要信守承诺
you keep your word.
兑现承诺 让客户满意
You deliver promises. You make customer happy.
而不是他妈的咬掉别人的脸！
Not bite fucking face off!
-明白了
-不
-Understood.
-No.
你害我损失了二十万
You just fucked me out of 200 grand.
你赔一个 我就赔两个
If you make one, I make two.
客户要她死 我也要她死
Customer wants her dead. I want her dead.
你去杀她 知道该带她去哪儿
You kill her. You know where to take her.
保证完成
Consider it done.
现在滚蛋！
Now fuck off!
这就滚 长官
Fucking off, sir.
卧槽 他气炸了
Holy shit, he was pissed.
何止气炸 差点连我俩都崩了
Fucking beyond. He was this close to smokin' us both.
得把那妞做了
We gotta whack that girl.
我没意见 干死那小贱人
Fine by me. Let's do the little bitch.
我们面对的是个恶魔
We are facing a devil.
这恶魔杀了我两名手下
This devil kills two soldiers.
淹死了沃洛迪米尔
He drowns Wolodymyr,
一位尊贵的船长
an esteemed captain.
现在又杀了我两个儿子
Now he kills my sons.
你理解我的担忧吗？
You do understand my concern?
迪米在哪儿？
Where is Dimi?
他难道不知道这恶魔是谁？
Won't he know who this devil is?
迪米在躲着
Dimi's hiding.
他们会帮你找到迪米
They will help you find Dimi.
感谢你告知此事
Thank you for bringing this to my attention.
现在走吧
Now go.
来点香槟吗？
Some champagne?
你父亲死了
Your father is dead.
他被绑在椅子上
Tied to a chair
淹死在自己的泳池里
and drowned in his pool.
所以这是好消息
So, it's good news.
杀他的那个人
The man who killed him
也杀了我儿子
murdered my sons.
丹雅和万科？
Danya and Vanko?
搞什么鬼？
What the fuck?
你不知道这事？
You did not know this?
我他妈怎么会知道？根本没人告诉我！
How the fuck would I know? Nobody tells me anything.
兄弟会把我当瘟神一样防着
The Brotherhood treats me like I'm radioactive.
这人是谁？
Who is this man?
我是好心问你
I ask with kindness.
我资助了一个有毒品渠道的飞车党
I bankroll biker gang with meth connection.
他们给我介绍了个真金白银的买家
They introduce me to buyer with real cash.
我们只碰面了五分钟
We met for five minutes.
仅此而已
That's it.
等等 等等 等一下
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
我有这个
I have this.
他在追杀你
He's hunting you.
找到他了
Found him.
-喂？
-您好 凯德先生？
-Hello?
-Hi. Mr. Cade?
这里是总部
This is the Main Office.
今天没人来接梅瑞狄斯
Um, no one's come to pick up Meredith today.
我马上到
I'll be right there.
-嘿 -今天还好吗？
-Hey. -Good day?
-挺好 -走吧
-Yeah. -Let's go.
爷爷呢？他从不会迟到
Where's Grandpa? He's never late.
他没回我消息
He's not answering me.
我给他发了快二十条信息
I sent him, like, 20 messages.
他肯定没事
I'm sure he's fine.
你没杀他吧？
You didn't kill him, did you?
老爸 我开玩笑的
Dad, I'm kidding.
你信我吗？
Do you trust me?
信啊
Yeah.
所以如果我告诉你一件事
So, if I tell you something,
你知道可以相信我 对吧？
you know you can believe me, right?
铺垫这么多只会更吓人
Okay, the build-up is just making it worse.
我犯了大错
I made a big mistake.
天啊 你真杀了爷爷？
Oh, my God. You did kill Grandpa.
梅瑞 我是认真的
Merry, I'm serious.
有些狠角色在追杀我
Some really bad people are after me,
我不想连累我爱的人受伤
and I don't want anyone I love to get hurt.
你和爷爷共享位置了吗？
Are you sharing your location with Grandpa?
嗯
Yeah.
你能看到他位置吗？
Can you see his location?
可能吧 我不确定
Maybe, I don't know.
老爸 他在家
Daddy, he's at home.
梅瑞 待在这儿别动 好吗？
Merry, stay here, okay?
梅瑞！待在那里！
Merry! Stay there!
爸爸 小心点！
Daddy, be careful!
他们是谁？
Who were they?
俄罗斯黑手党？
Russian mafia?
对
Yes.
他们是来找你的
They were looking for you.
这事全因你而起
This happened because of you.
暴力如影随形跟着你
Violence follows you like a cloud.
他本可以不管你 爷爷
He could've left you in there, Grandpa.
他救了你的命
He saved your life.
这点我承认
I can acknowledge that.
你该去医院
You should go to the hospital.
那里安全
You'll be safe there.
我会照顾梅瑞
I'll take care of Merry.
该让警察处理了
It's time o let the cops handle this.
警察拦不住他们
Cops can't stop them.
好吧
All right.
之后再说
We'll figure it out later.
还有 莱文
And, Levon,
谢谢
thank you.
记得冈尼吗？
You remember Gunny?
你那个瞎了眼却不自知的哥们？
Your blind friend who doesn't know he's blind?
就是他
That's the one.
他在乡下有栋房子
He has a country house.
风暴过去前我们待那儿安全
We'll be safe there till the storm passes.
嗨
Hi.
想进来吗？来吧
You wanna come inside? Come on.
-饿吗？
-永远饿
-You hungry?
-Always.
-你呢？
-嗯
-And you?
-Yeah.
老兄 出啥事了？
What happened, man?
惹错人了 对吧？
You fuck with the wrong people, huh?
嘿 你本可以拦住我
Hey, you could've stopped me.
这世上谁能拦得住你？
What force on earth is gonna stop you?
情况越来越糟了
It's gettin' ugly.
你真能找到那姑娘？没吹牛吧？
Can you find this girl? Can you really find this girl?
我能找到
I can find her.
我会带她回家
I'm gonna bring her home.
听着像回事 有计划吗？
I hear that. You got a plan?
直接去问迪米那家伙她在哪儿
I'm gonna ask this Dimi fella where she is.
所有线索都指向他
All roads lead to him.
你靠杀人闯进这浑水
Now, you killed your way into this,
也得靠杀人才能脱身
you're gonna have to kill your way out of it.
我早料到了
I figured as much.
我能帮你一把
I can help you with that.
是吗？
Oh, yeah?
给你看点东西
Let me show you somethin'.
您先请 长官
After you, sir.
今晚我来当你的“武器侍酒师”
All right, I will be your weapons sommelier
为您服务
for this evening.
绕过这面墙
If you come around this wall,
你会看到AK自动步枪
you see the Avtomat Kalashnikov,
从1947年就开始杀美国人
been killing Americans since 1947.
还有从萨达姆宫殿里搞来的土豪镀金版
Also, comes in a deluxe, blingy version pulled direct from Saddam's palace.
这边是M4卡宾枪
What you got over here is the M-Four Carbine,
反恐战争里的雪佛兰黑斑羚
it's the Chevy Impala of the war on terror.
这把MP5 SD适合暗杀
Beautiful MP5 SD here if you wanna kill somebody,
杀人时不会吵醒邻居
but you don't wanna wake 'em up.
但这才是真正的猛兽
But this is the real beast here.
天启四骑士的原始武器之一
One of the original weapons of the four horsemen of the apocalypse.
M14步枪
The M14.
你可能记得这家伙
You might remember this weapon.
不想记得 但确实记得
I don't want to, but I do.
拿去吧
There you go.
得把序列号钻掉
I'll have to drill out the serial numbers.
不用 已经处理好了
Oh, no, that's already done.
这些枪从未存在过 哪儿都没有
These were never here. Never anywhere.
就像我们当年一样
Kinda like us,
来无影去无踪
back in the day.
兄弟 咱们当年干的可都是正义之事
We did some righteous shit, brother.
没错
Yeah, we did.
-里面是啥？-不关你事
-What's in there? -None of your business.
我能一起去吗？
Can I come?
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
那学校怎么办？
What about school?
最多缺几天课
You'll miss a couple of days, at most.
我几乎见不到你
I barely see you.
我不想你惹上麻烦
I don't want you getting in trouble.
那样就永远见不到你了
Then I'll never see you.
不会的
That's not gonna happen.
看这个？这是你
See this? This is you.
一人一半
Half and half.
我要你保管好这个
I want you to hold onto this.
我会回来取的
I'm comin' back for that.
好
Okay.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你 爸爸
Love you, Daddy.
爸爸 我不想你受伤
Daddy, I don't want you getting hurt.
我很快就回来 好吗？
I'll be back soon, okay?
冈尼 照顾好她
Gunny, take good care of her.
当然
Yeah, of course.
-谢谢 乔伊斯 -这边走
-Thank you, Joyce. -This way.
-再见 莱文 -保重 宝贝
-Bye, Levon. -All right, sweetheart.
“我们的天父
"Our Father,
愿你的名受显扬
who art in heaven,
愿你的国来临
hallowed be thy name,
愿你的旨意奉行在人间……”
thy kingdom come,
上帝不在这儿 小甜心
thy will be done."
睡美人醒啦？
God ain't here, sweetheart.
要给你灌点安眠药吗……
Have a nice nap, Princess?
-靠边停车！-嘿 冷静！
We gotta pull over and load this bitch with some fuckin' sleeping pills...
-操你妈的贱人！
-别动手！
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-停车！ -快抓住她！
-Fucking bitch! -Hey, take it easy!
-停车！-妈的！
-Pull over! -Come on! Stop!
-抓住那贱人！
-停车！停车！
Fucking get it, fucking bitch.
操！我的枪呢！
Fucking grab that bitch!
操！
Pull over! Pull over! Pull over!
天杀的！
God damn it! Where's my fucking gun!
操！
Fuck!
妈的
Fuck.
快他妈动啊 毒蛇！
Fuckin' move, Viper!
操！操！
Fuck! Fuck!
这他妈怎么回事？
I mean, what the fuck?
她跑得真快
She is fast.
我们他妈要回监狱了！
We're going back to fuckin' prison!
懂吗？
Huh?
懂吗？ 你懂吗？
Huh? You get it?
懂 我懂
Yeah, I get it. I get it.
操！冷静
Fuck! Okay, okay.
操！操！
Fuck! Fuck!
妈的
Shit.
天才 现在咋办？
Okay, genius, now what?
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
我叫珍妮·加西亚 我被绑架了
My name is Jenny Garcia. I was kidnapped.
没事了 我们知道你是谁
It's all right. We know who you are.
送你回家
Let's get you home.
好
Okay.
我他妈真抱歉
I'm so fucking sorry.
想我了吗？
Miss me?
操！
Fuck!
爆了这贱人的头！
Fucking dome the bitch!
-开玩笑吧？
-是他吗？
-You gotta be kidding me.
-Is that him?
搞什么鬼？
What the fuck?
操 是视频通话
Fuck, it's a video call.
接着手机！给我枪……
Here, take the fucking phone! Give me the...
-操！-……他妈的枪
-Fuck! -...God damn fucking gun.
长官
Hey, sir.
迪米说那妞还在你们手上
Dimi says you still have the girl.
对 对 还在
Uh, yeah, yeah. We still got her.
证明她还活着
Show me she's still alive.
看 还活着
See? Still alive.
今晚在农场二次交易 一百万
I want a second date tonight, at the farmhouse. One million dollars.
行 您说了算 长官
Uh, yeah. Whatever you want, sir.
我会把她洗干净喷香等着您
I'll get her cleaned up and smelling real pretty for you.
不 我要她脏兮兮的
No, no, no. I want her dirty.
别让她睡着
Not sleepy,
但要脏着活着
but dirty and alive.
暂时活着
For now.
-操 没问题   -遵命
-Fuck, yeah.
不 不 不 我要她鲜活的模样
No, no, no. I want her dirty.
不是昏昏欲睡
Not sleepy,
而是鲜活又生动
but dirty and alive.
暂时如此
For now.
-操 爽啊 -哦 没错
-Fuck, yeah. -Oh, yes.
该用哪本护照？
Which passport, okay?
你给了我这么多本
You sent me all these passports.
我分不清 红的？蓝的？绿的？
I can't tell. Red? Blue? Green?
-我哪知道颜色？直接告诉我 -我们要去哪？
-I don't know what color, just tell me. - -Where are we going?
什么？行 好 走吧
What? Okay. Yeah. Go.
我全带上总行了吧？
I take all of them, okay?
-你要什么？钱吗？-不 我不...
-What do you want? You want money? -No, I don't...
给 拿钱 全拿去
Here, take your money. You take money.
老子不要你的臭钱！
I don't want your fucking money!
-钱全归你 -我不稀罕
-You take all the money. -I don't want
-你的臭钱！-全拿走 行了吧？
-your fucking money! -You take all the money, okay?
-让我帮你！-不 不用帮
-Let me help you! -No, no, I don't need help.
操
Fuck.
滚开！住手！
Get away! Stop!
明天开始 戒断治疗
Starting tomorrow, rehab.
你只会放任我在泥潭里越陷越深
All you do is let me slip down slippery slope.
你本该是我的支柱
You're supposed to be my rock.
就像人们说的 "她是我的靠山"
You know, like they say, "Oh, she's my rock."
"多谢了 "可你根本不配
"Hey, thank you." I have nothing to thank you for.
知道吗？你就是个纵容者
You know what? You are just an enabler.
他来了！
he's here!
行
Okay.
行 你表态了
Okay. You made your point.
现在谈条件 你从此
Now we make a deal, and you begin
当个有钱人 如何？
a new life as a wealthy man, huh?
我能自力更生
I can pay my own bills.
恭喜啊
Congrats.
-再靠近她就死 -别！
-Come closer and she dies. -No!
我料到了
I figured that.
你该消失 拿钱走人
You should disappear. Take the money.
过好日子去
Make a nice life.
她在哪？
Where is she?
我不认识这女人
I do not know this woman.
你撒谎太烂
You're a bad liar.
何必赌上一切？
Why risk everything?
为何为她杀这么多人？
Why kill everyone for her?
因为我承诺护她周全
'Cause I told her I had her back.
如果我交出这女人
If I give you this woman,
能活命吗？
you let me live?
要是我直接给地址
Because if I just give you the address,
你会毙了我吧？
then you shoot me, huh?
若你给假地址 我再毙你呢？
What if you give me a fake address and I shoot you?
两败俱伤罢了
That's bad for both of us.
沿57号公路往南
Head south on 57.
到了再给你地址
Then I give you her address.
走
Let's go.
你认识这人？
You know this guy?
当然 他是蝰蛇
Of course, I know. He's Viper.
人力资源部主管
He's Chief of Human Resource Department
专招特殊项目人手
and recruiting for special projects.
为一个妓女豁出命？
Why you do all this for a whore?
再说一遍
Say it again.
有胆再说
Please, say that again.
果然怂了
Thought so.
听着 迪米
Okay, Dimi,
说目的地
tell me where we're going.
她在哪？
Where is she?
那里
There.
她在里面？
She's in there?
对
She's there.
没骗我？
Promise?
保证
I promise.
就在里面
She's there.
为何是她？
Why her?
谁定的？
Who decides?
蝰蛇去夜店
Viper goes to club,
拍下漂亮姑娘
takes pictures of pretty girls.
我发给客户 他们挑
I send them to clients, they make choice.
安排见面
Meeting is arranged.
这是我的专长服务
This is my specialty service.
像买雪地胎一样简单
Like shopping for a set of snow tires.
她们是人！
These are human beings.
你以为钱会在乎
You think money gives a shit
来源干不干净？
where it comes from?
我不干这行
If I didn't do this,
别人也会干
somebody else would.
你还没说为何追杀我们
You still haven't told me why.
为何猎杀我们？
Why do you hunt us?
你有闺女吗？
You have a daughter?
没有
No.
那你永远不懂
Then you won't understand.
嘿 干得漂亮
Hey, good lookin' out.
兄弟 没事吧？
Hey, yo, we good, brother?
差得远呢
Man, we far from good.
和迪米搭线那混蛋
That motherfucker we hooked up with Dimi
今晚宰了半打俄国佬
clapped out half a dozen Russians tonight.
据说正往迪米的窝点去
Rumor is, he's on his way to Dimi's trap house right now.
所有人
Everybody,
抄家伙！
mount the fuck up!
照他说的做！抄家伙！
You heard the man. Mount up!
真他妈好笑
That's funny shit.
听着不错啊 大小姐
Sounds lovely, Princess.
我不认同这种行为
I don't condone this behavior,
但我的账户喜欢
but my bank account does.
嘿 到点了
Hey. It's time.
还磨蹭什么？赶紧！
What the fuck are we still doing here? Come on.
我去叫那变态
Yeah. I'll get the pervert.
咱们都是棋子 小子 别往心里去
We're all just numbers, kid. Nothin' personal.
我觉得挺私人的
Feels pretty fuckin' personal to me.
该走了 先生
We have to go now, sir.
为什么？
Why?
机不可失
It's now or never.
那就走
Then it's now.
我哪里得罪你了？
What have I done to you?
没有
Nothing.
这才有趣
That's the best part.
我好奇你的内脏...
I wonder what you look like on...
长什么样
the inside.
刚什么动静？
The fuck was that?
哇哦
whoa.
莱文！
Levon!
他们在开枪？
Are they fucking shooting?
现在谁要完蛋了 嗯？
Who's gonna get fucked now, huh?
他在里面
He's in there.
正在扫射
Shooting the place up.
所有人
Everybody,
上膛
lock and load.
去宰了那杂种
Let's go get this motherfucker.
你俩跟我
Yeah, you two on me.
照他说的做！跟上！
You heard the man. Come on.
保持紧凑 右侧掩护
Stay tight, stay right.
恶魔 破窗进去
Demon, put it through the glass.
没问题
You got it.
莱文！
Levon!
闭嘴！
Shut the fuck up!
没事的 会好的
Hey. It's gonna be okay.
是吗？
Yeah?
你只管...对
You just... Yeah.
我开始觉得
I'm beginning to think
你根本不知道自己在干嘛！
that you do not know what you are doing!
别慌 先生
Don't worry, sir.
一切尽在掌控
Everything's under control.
我保证
I promise you.
我要挖出你的心
I'm gonna cut your heart out.
尽管试试
Good luck.
你真名叫什么？
What the fuck is your real name?
莱文
Levon.
幸会 莱文
Nice to meet you, Levon.
准备好了吗 小子？
You ready, son?
时刻准备着
I'm always ready.
本不想与你为敌
My fight wasn't with you.
我懂 兄弟
I know, brother.
做个了结吧
Finish it.
对不住了 兄弟
Sorry, brother.
-莱文！-搞什么鬼？
-Levon! -What the fuck?
你敢闯进来？
How dare you come in here?
-操！该死！-妈的！
-Fuck! Shit! -Oh, fuck!
这下糟了
Oh, that is not good.
什么情况？
What the fuck?
-撑住 -换弹！
-Hang on. -Reload!
等等 等等
wait, wait, wait.
不 别！
No, no, no!
-我能解释！-操！
-I can explain everything! -Fuck!
不！
No!
妈的
Oh, shit.
妈妈！
Mommy!
操！
Fuck!
该死！
臭婊子！
Fuckin' bitch!
操
Fuck.
去死！
Fuck you!
结束了
It's over now.
去死吧 贱人！
Fucking die, bitch!
我好像杀了她
I think I killed her.
很好
Good.
操
Fuck.
哇哦
Whoa.
跟紧我
Stay on my six.
什么意思？
What's that mean?
跟着我
Follow me.
里面有枪手
There's an active shooter in there.
该死
Shit.
干掉他
Let's kill this guy.
刚才什么声音？
What was that?
蓝牙
Bluetooth.
那是手雷？
Is that a grenade?
捂好耳朵
Mind your ears.
哦
Oh.
准备好了？
You ready?
没
No.
该走了
Time to go.
黄泉路上见
See you on the other side.
那是什么？
What was that?
对老友的敬意
Respect for an old friend.
准备好回家了吗？
You ready to go home?
快带我离开这鬼地方
Get me the hell outta here.
是 大哥
Yes, my brother.
他逃了...
He escaped...
带着那女孩
with the girl.
这不是生意
None of this was business.
恶魔得到了他想要的
The devil has what he came for.
放他走
Let him go.
我明白组织需低调行事
I understand our need to move quietly in the world.
但我不会放过
But I will not turn the other cheek
杀我手足的仇人
to the man who killed my children.
那我们就杀了你
Then we will kill you.
兄弟会高于个人私仇
The Brotherhood comes before your personal vengeance.
明白吗？
Do you understand?
明白
I understand.
告密者不得好死
snitches get stitches.
闺女！天啊！
¡Mija! Oh, my God.
-对不起 真的对不起 -不 别这样
-I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. -No. No.
不 别道歉
No. No.
莱文！
Levon!
谢谢 真的谢谢你
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
我想带梅丽
I was thinking about taking Merry
去鸡舍看看
out to the chicken coop today.
-想去吗？-想
-Yeah, would you like that? -Yeah.
-嗯 -不知道
-Yeah. -I don't know.
小心那只暴躁的老公鸡
You better watch out for that old grumpy one.
它超凶的
He's mean. He's mean.
哦不 它超凶
Oh, no. He's mean.
爸 是你！你回来了
Hey, Dad, it's you! You came back.
说过会回来的
Told you I would.
你没事吧 爸爸？
You're okay, Daddy?
嗯 刮胡子蹭破点皮
Yeah. I nicked myself shaving.
嗨
Hi.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
嘿 乔伊斯
Hey, Joyce.
全须全尾的
You're in one piece.
勉强吧
Just about.
看来他们没干掉你？
Well, I guess they didn't kill you, huh?
没 但尽力了
Nah. They really tried their best.
找到那姑娘了？
You found that girl?
找到了
I found her.
我错过了什么？
So, what did I miss?
我交了乌鸦和猫头鹰朋友
Well, I made friends with a crow and an owl.
还有只山羊会叫我的名字
And there's a goat I taught to say my name.
-不可能 -真的！
-No. -Yeah.
我对着它说话
It was really cool. I was just talking,
然后它就叫："梅丽！
and then it was like, "Merry!
梅丽！"
"Merry!"
欢迎回来 兄弟
Welcome back, brother.
到家了
You're home.
Powered by Deepseek & Spyro